colgate.edu 2019-06-22

# Privacy Policy for Colgate University

Colgate is committed to safeguarding all personal information that we obtain about our customers and consumers both on-line and off-line.

We do not routinely collect any personal information about you when you visit a Colgate website. We only collect personal information that is voluntarily given to Colgate by our users. 

We do not share any nonpublic personal information with any nonaffiliated third-party vendors without your consent. If we were to share any nonpublic personal information with nonaffiliated third parties, we would give you a reasonable amount of time to opt out. We will only share your nonpublic personal information with third parties when the following condition applies:

\-- We have your consent to share your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties "as permitted by law" or when it is necessary to provide the product or service that you are requesting.

However, you should be aware that we do collect information about the IP address of the domain from which you accessed the Internet, the date and time you accessed our site, the pages you visited and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. 

This information is not shared with anyone beyond the support staff to this home page except when required by law and it is only used as a source of tracking statistical information. All users' personal information is restricted in our offices. 

Only employees who need sensitive information to perform a specific job are granted access to a user's personal information. The servers that we store personal information on are kept in a secure environment that is locked when not being monitored. Colgate is not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites that we link to or how they treat their users' sensitive information.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify you of any changes on our website so everyone may be aware of the change and how it will affect our users. If you have any questions or comments about this policy, you may e-mail us at [privacy@colgate.edu](mailto:privacy@colgate.edu).
